A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Associates, Gene W. Setzer papers FA1233
Rockefeller Archive Center
Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Associates, Gene W. Setzer papers
1978-1989
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
Setzer, Gene W.
FA1233
2.28 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research in accordance with the terms of donation from the Laurance S. Rockefeller estate (2009). Brittle or damaged materials are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order as received.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of Gene W. Setzer's meeting records and reports collected during his service on the Boards of Jackson Hole Preserve and Sleepy Hollow Restorations (which officially became known as Historic Hudson Valley in 1988).
The meeting records represented primarily include: Annual Meeting of Members, Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, Finance Committee, Property Committee, and all associated reports including financial reports and analyis. Some files are accompanied by Setzer's meeting notes.
Biographical / Historical
Gene W. Setzer's career in philanthropic admininstration included executive positions with the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, the National Audubon Society, and his service as an associate to Laurance S. Rockefeller and the Rockefeller family.
- Jackson Hole Preserve Inc. (JHPI) - Annual Meetings of Members, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Meetings 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Meetings and Reports 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - A Preliminary Interpretive Plan for Kykuit, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Associates Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Meetings and Reports 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Meetings and Reports 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Meetings and Reports 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7, Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Meetings and Reports 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations (SHR) - Meetings and Reports 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5-6, Box 4, Folder 1-4)
- Historic Hudson Valley (HHV) - Meetings and Reports 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5-6, Box 5, Folder 1)
- Historic Hudson Valley (HHV) - Meetings and Reports 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2-5, Box 6, Folder 1-3)